questions = [
    {
        "question": "What is the general formula for alkanes?",
        "correctAnswer": "CₙH₂ₙ₊₂",
        "answer0": "CₙH₂ₙ",
        "answer1": "CₙHₙ",
        "answer2": "C₂ₙH₂ₙ₊₂",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the general formula for alkenes?",
        "correctAnswer": "CₙH₂ₙ",
        "answer0": "C₂ₙH₂ₙ₊₂",
        "answer1": "CₙHₙ",
        "answer2": "CₙH₂ₙ₊₂",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the functional group for alcohols?",
        "correctAnswer": "-OH",
        "answer0": "-COOH",
        "answer1": "C=C",
        "answer2": "-COO-",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the functional group for alkenes?",
        "correctAnswer": "C=C",
        "answer0": "-OH",
        "answer1": "-COOH",
        "answer2": "-COO-",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the functional group for alkanes?",
        "correctAnswer": "C-C",
        "answer0": "-OH",
        "answer1": "-COOH",
        "answer2": "-COO-",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the functional group for carboxylic acids?",
        "correctAnswer": "-COOH",
        "answer0": "C=C",
        "answer1": "-COO-",
        "answer2": "C-C",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the functional group for esters?",
        "correctAnswer": "-COO-",
        "answer0": "C-C",
        "answer1": "-COOH",
        "answer2": "-OH",
    },
    {
        "question": "How can you separate a mixture of alkanes?",
        "correctAnswer": "Fractional Distillation",
        "answer0": "Complete Distillation",
        "answer1": "Distillation",
        "answer2": "Percentage Distillation",
    },
    {
        "question": "How can you separate a long chain of alkanes?",
        "correctAnswer": "Cracking",
        "answer0": "Fractional Distillation",
        "answer1": "Complete Distillation",
        "answer2": "Percentage Distillation",
    },
    {
        "question": "What test do you use to distinguish alkanes and alkenes?",
        "correctAnswer": "Bromine Test",
        "answer0": "Iodine Test",
        "answer1": "Chemistry Test",
        "answer2": "Barium Chloride Test",
    },
    {
        "question": "What happens when you add alkanes to bromine?",
        "correctAnswer": "Stays Orange",
        "answer0": "Gas Produced",
        "answer1": "Turns Colourless",
        "answer2": "Solid precipitate formed",
    },
    {
        "question": "What happens when you add alkenes to bromine?",
        "correctAnswer": "Turns Colourless",
        "answer0": "Solid precipitate formed",
        "answer1": "Stays orange",
        "answer2": "Gas Produced",
    }
]